techzillo.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Techzillo

Updated May 31, 2018

At Techzillo, we take online privacy seriously and we respect the concerns of our community of users. In this policy we describe our privacy practices with regard to information we collect through Techzillo.com, to help you make informed decisions about how you share information when you visit or use the Site.

### Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at [info@techzillo.com](malto:info@techzillo.com) and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

**Understanding How Information Is Collected on Techzillo:**

**Information You May Choose to Provide to Us**

We may collect information, including personally identifiable information, directly from you if you choose to provide that information. For example, you may provide us with your name and contact information (such as an email address), date of birth, or other details of that nature, when you sign up for our newsletters or participate in promotions or surveys on the Site.

You also may choose to provide personally identifiable information about yourself when you participate in forums or discussions on the Site. Please be aware that information you post in these forums may be viewed or captured by anyone who visits the Site, therefore you should avoid posting sensitive or personal information that you would not want to be available to the public.

**Information That Is Automatically Collected When You Visit Techzillo**

When you access the Site, we and our third-party partners and vendors may automatically collect certain information about your visit using tools such as cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies. The information collected automatically when you visit the Site may include your IP address, characteristics of your operating system, information about your browser and system settings, data about the computer or mobile device you use to access the Site, unique device identifiers, clickstream data (which shows the page-by-page path you take as you browse the Site), and other details that generally are not considered personally identifiable.

**Cookies**  are small files that websites and other online services use to store information about users on the users’ own computers. This Site may use cookies (such as HTTP and HTML5 cookies and Flash cookies), as well as other types of local storage. For more information about cookies, you may visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). See the section below regarding Your choices to learn more about how you may limit or disable cookies on your computer. If you choose to disable cookies, that could affect certain features of the Site that use cookies to enhance their functionality.

To manage our automatic data collection, we may place tags (often referred to as “web beacons”) on pages on the Site or in emails we send to you.  **Web beacons**  are small files that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies, and they may be used for a variety of purposes, such as counting the number of visitors to the Site, analyzing how users navigate around the Site, assessing how many emails that we send are actually opened and which articles or links are viewed by visitors.

We also use third-party web analytics services, such as Google Analytics, on the Site, to provide us with statistics and other information about visitors to the Site. [Click here to learn more about Google Analytics and how you may opt out.](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)

**“Do Not Track” Signals.**  Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “do not track” signal to websites and online services you visit. At this time there is no consensus among industry participants as to the meaning of “do not track” in this context. Like many other websites, Techzillo.com is not configured to respond to “do not track” signals from browsers. [Click here to learn more about “do not track” signals.](https://allaboutdnt.com/)

Finally, companies that provide certain third-party apps, tools, widgets, and plug-ins that may appear on the Site (for example, Facebook “Like” buttons) also may use automated means to collect information regarding your interactions with these features. This information collection is subject to the privacy policies or notices of those providers.

**How We May Use Information We Collect**

We may use the information gathered on Techzillo for various purposes, including the purposes listed below. For example, if you were to contact us with a question and provide your email address, we would use the email address you provided to respond to your inquiry. In addition, we use information we collect from you and through the Site to:

  * Provide products and services you request (such as when you sign up to receive our email newsletters);
  * Respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support;
  * Offer you products and services, or direct you to portions of this Site or other websites, that we believe may interest you;
  * Communicate about, and administer your participation in, events, programs, contests, and other offers or promotions;
  * Carry out, evaluate, and improve our business (which may include developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications);
  * Perform data analytics regarding usage of the Site (including market and customer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal information);
  * Guard against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements, law enforcement requests, and our company policies.

**How We May Share Information**

Our agents, vendors, consultants, and other service providers may have access to information we collect through the Site to carry out work on our behalf. Those parties are restricted from using personal information collected through the Site for purposes other than to provide the requested assistance. In addition, certain service providers may collect or access information through the Site to enable or provide services, tools, or other features available on the Site. We also may share information:

  * With our affiliates for internal business purposes;
  * If we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena);
  * In response to requests from government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities;
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity;
  * With respect to analytics and statistical information, to inform advertisers about the nature of our user base;
  * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation); and
  * With your consent or at your discretion.

**Your Choices**

**Unsubscribe from emails.**  To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of that email newsletter. If you would like to globally opt-out from all Techzillo email campaigns, please send an email to  _[info@techzillo.com](mailto:info@techzillo.com)_  with “Unsubscribe” in the subject line. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honour your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.

**Blocking cookies.**  Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies, or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Site that use cookies to enhance their functionality.

**Disabling local shared objects (“Flash cookies”).**  We may use other kinds of local storage that function similarly, but are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies. Your browser may allow you to disable its HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in its HTML5 local storage. [Click here](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html) for details about deleting information contained in “local shared objects” or adjusting related preferences.

**Options concerning third-party ad networks.**  For more information about third-party ad networks and services that use these technologies, you can visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and [click here](http://aboutads.info/choices) to opt out or to learn more about your options. You also may visit the [NAI’s site for additional options](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) on how to opt out of interest-based advertising.

**How We Protect Personal Information.**

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. That said, it is not possible to guarantee the security of information transmitted online, and you assume some risk with regard to the security of information you provide through any website, including this Site. If you have a data security inquiry, you may contact us by emailing  _[info@techzillo.com](mailto:info@techzillo.com)_.

**Links From Techzillo to Other Websites**

On this Site, we may provide links to other websites that are controlled by third parties. Linked websites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. We are not responsible for the content, usage terms, privacy policies, or any other aspects of websites that we do not own or control.

**Surveys, Quizzes and Other Features**

While you are visiting Techzillo, you may have the opportunity to participate in surveys or quizzes, or to use other interactive features that request information about you and your opinions and preferences. Your participation in these features is entirely voluntary. If you do choose to participate, please be aware that these features may be operated by a third party that is not controlled by Techzillo, and therefore the information you provide may be collected by the third party and subject to its privacy policy.

**Children’s Privacy**

This Site is not designed or intended for use by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete any such information.

**Information for Users Outside the United Kingdom**

If you are visiting Techzillo from outside the United Kingdom, please be aware that information we collect through the Site will be transferred to and stored on servers in the United Kingdom. By using this Site, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer and processing of your personal data in the United Kingdom as described in this online privacy policy. Please be aware that the data protection laws and regulations applicable to your personal data transferred to the United Kingdom may be different from the laws in your country of residence.

**How We’ll Inform You About Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update this online privacy policy periodically to reflect changes to our privacy practices, such as how we collect or use personal information. We will we indicate at the top of this privacy policy the date when it was most recently updated.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about this policy or about our privacy practices, you may contact us by emailing  _[info@techzillo.com](mailto:info@techzillo.com)_.
